Precious Chinenye Ndigwe

E-mail: pndigwe23@gmail.com § Phone: 08106500629 no 1 super master close, diamond estate,, amuwo odofin, Lagos State

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Strategic Marketing and Communications Consultant with a firm grasp of corporate messaging and branding. Possesses a strong work ethic, as well as exceptional writing, editing, and research skills. Exceptional leader talented at big data analysis, customer support, quality control, task management and Technically-savvy with outstanding relationship building, training and presentation skills. Flexible and hardworking in deadline-driven environments. Experienced IT personnel committed to maintaining cutting-edge technical skills and up-to-date industry knowledge.

SKILLS

- Superior verbal and written communication skills
- Excellent interpersonal skills
- Exceptional attention to detail
- Calm under pressure
- Excellent media contacts
- Fluent in English
- Creative and innovative

WORK EXPERIENCE

GoodMan Training Institute

June 2013 — April 2014

Computer Basic/ Web Design Tutor

- Training students on the basis of using the computer and introduction to front-end web design.
- Created curriculum and planned course content and methods of instruction.
- Increased enrollment by 20% in Adult Continuing education and Enrichment programs by offering new and innovative programming.
- Wrote and designed continuing education examinations.
- Instructed students on a variety of skills, including web design, creativity e.t.c.
- Assigned lessons and corrected homework.
- Developed detailed daily lesson plans for activities.

Mayakorp Nigeria

May 2017 — Nov 2017

Technical / IT Support Intern

- Evaluated potential software products based on new and existing system development and migration requirements.
- Upgraded and expanded network systems and their components.
- Documented all server and network problems and other unusual events in detail.

Precious Chinenve Ndigwe

- Incorporated feedback and recommendations from other staff members when modifying the software.
- Performed initial client assessment and analysis to begin the research process.
- Advocated for end-users to perform testing and problem analysis for the server, desktop and IT infrastructure work.

JustFantastic

Jun 2017 — Feb 2018

Online Shop/ Catalog Manager

- Online Shop/ Catalogue Manager editing product images/uploads on the e-commerce site.
- Content writing/management for individual products, product Search engine optimization, and vendor registration.
- Designed strategic plan for component development practices to support future projects.
- Managed creative projects from concept to completion while managing outside vendors.
- Communicated with vendors regarding back order availability, future inventory and special orders.
- Contacted customer to follow up on purchases, suggest new merchandise, and inform them about promotions and upcoming events.

Bring It On Africa

may 2018 — present

Technical / IT Support / Media

- Designed strategic plan for component development practices to support undergoing projects.
- Evaluated and responded to incoming sales leads and requests for technical support assistance.
- Provided base level IT support to non-technical personnel within the business.
- Resolved customer issues in a clear, courteous and straightforward manner.
- Managed call flow and responded to technical support needs of team members.
- Defined clear targets and objectives and communicated them to other team members.

EDUCATION

BSc in Computer Science

November 2014 — August 2018

Nnamdi Azikiwe University

Second class lower

SSCE / WASCE

February 2012 — August 2013

St. John of God Girls Secondary Shool

QUALIFICATIONS

- Kaspersky Endpoint Security Associate
- Kaspersky Endpoint Security and Management Small Business Certification
- Google Digital Garage Online Marketing Fundamentals Qualification
- NetApp Virtualization Technology Fundamentals Certification

REFERENCES

Precious Chinenye Ndigwe 2

Prince Henry Ikechukwu Ndigwe. Email: ndigwehenry@gmail.com

Phone: 08066425357

Precious Chinenye Ndigwe 3